Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
=In The Name of Loyalty=
=باسم الولاء=
=Episode 23=
=الحلقة 23=
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحياتي جلالتك.
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
- تحياتي، جلالة الملك.
I brought the seal. Release them.
لقد أحضرت الختم. أطلق سراحهم.
Imperial Weaving House's Master and assassin Cheng Ge
سيد بيت النسيج الإمبراطوري والقاتل تشنغ جي
plotted to assassinate His Majesty.
خططوا لاغتيال جلالته.
His Majesty is young and lacks judgment,
جلالته شاب ويفتقر إلى الحكمة،
misplacing his trust.
وضع ثقته في غير محلها.
The imperial seal shall now be managed by the Prince Regent
سيتم الآن إدارة الختم الإمبراطوري بواسطة الأمير الوصي
to secure the realm.
لتأمين المملكة.
I
أنا
will not fail Your Majesty.
لن تخذل جلالتك.
I will perform virtuous deeds
سأقوم بالأعمال الفاضلة
and seek prosperity for the people.
والسعي لتحقيق الرخاء للشعب.
- We shall not fail Your Majesty
- لن نخذل جلالتك
- and seek prosperity for the people.
- واطلب الرخاء للناس.
Release them.
أطلق سراحهم.
Your Majesty, you are not wise.
جلالتك، أنت لست حكيما.
These two bound here are treasonous rebels
هذين الاثنين المقيدين هنا هم متمردين خائنين
and eternal criminals who attempted regicide.
والمجرمين الأبديين الذين حاولوا قتل الملك.
Release them.
أطلق سراحهم.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Your Majesty, though you are compassionate,
يا صاحب الجلالة، على الرغم من أنك رحيم،
these two individuals
هذين الفردين
do carry legitimate suspicion of assassination attempts.
هل تحمل شكوكًا مشروعة بشأن محاولات الاغتيال؟
However,
لكن،
between them,
بينهم
one is the mastermind
واحد هو العقل المدبر
and the other an accomplice.
والآخر شريك.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Now,
الآن،
the accomplice may be spared,
قد يتم تجنيب الشريك،
but the mastermind
لكن العقل المدبر
must be executed.
يجب تنفيذه.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Who is the mastermind?
من هو العقل المدبر؟
Who is the accomplice?
من هو الشريك؟
Since you address me as Lord Father,
وبما أنك تخاطبني بـ "الرب الآب"،
I bear the duty to guide your conduct.
إنني أتحمل واجب توجيه سلوكك.
Today's matter
مسألة اليوم
is my lesson for you on discerning right from wrong.
هذا درسي لك في التمييز بين الصواب والخطأ.
Who is the mastermind? And who is the accomplice?
من هو العقل المدبر؟ ومن هو الشريك؟
Please make the judgment yourself.
من فضلك قم بالحكم بنفسك.
Did the weaving house's Master
هل كان سيد بيت النسيج
train assassin Cheng Ge to kill Your Majesty?
هل تدرب القاتل تشنغ جي على قتل جلالتك؟
Or did Cheng Ge of Pingxiang lineage
أو فعل Cheng Ge من سلالة Pingxiang
manipulate the weaving house's Master into regicide?
التلاعب بسيد بيت النسيج حتى يقتل الملك؟
This matter today
هذا الأمر اليوم
requires an explanation to the entire court.
يتطلب توضيحا للمحكمة بأكملها.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
indecisiveness
التردد
is no virtue.
لا يوجد فضيلة.
I'll count to three.
سأحسب إلى ثلاثة.
If you cannot decide,
إذا لم تتمكن من اتخاذ القرار،
then I
ثم انا
will have to choose in your stead.
سيتعين عليك الاختيار بدلاً منك.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Shield His Highness!
حماية سموه!
Nan!
في!
Your Highness, hurry!
سموكم، اسرعوا!
Master!
يتقن!
Live well.
عش جيدا.
Be a good Emperor.
كن امبراطورا جيدا.
I'll never let anyone bully you again.
لن اسمح لأحد أن يتنمر عليك مرة أخرى.
Okay.
تمام.
Master.
يتقن.
Master!
يتقن!
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Cheng Ge.
تشنغ قه.
Master!
يتقن!
Master.
يتقن.
Nan.
في.
Master!
يتقن!
Nan!
في!
Your Grace, spare me!
يا صاحب السمو، أنقذني!
Zhiying!
تشي ينغ!
Ji.
من.
You can't kill him now.
لا يمكنك قتله الآن.
Do you know what he's done to me?
هل تعلم ماذا فعل بي؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I'm begging you.
انا أتوسل إليك.
Endure a bit more, okay?
تحمل أكثر قليلا، حسنا؟
Endure a bit more.
تحمل قليلا أكثر.
It'll all be over soon.
كل شيء سينتهي قريبا.
How's the wedding banquet
كيف كان حفل الزفاف؟
preparation?
تحضير؟
My lord,
سيدي،
everything's ready.
كل شيء جاهز.
It begins at noon.
ويبدأ عند الظهر.
Good.
جيد.
Why haven't you killed me yet?
لماذا لم تقتلني بعد؟
No need to rush.
لا داعي للتسرع.
I've arranged
لقد رتبت
the way you die.
الطريقة التي تموت بها.
On the wedding day,
في يوم الزفاف،
an assassin appeared.
ظهر قاتل.
Prince Regent Gao Ji captured Cheng Ge,
استولى الأمير الوصي قاو جي على تشنغ جي،
the assassin planted by His Majesty's side
القاتل المزروع بجانب جلالته
under the guise of a waiting maid.
تحت ستار خادمة منتظرة.
Yet unfortunately, His Majesty
ولكن للأسف جلالته
was assassinated.
تم اغتياله.
Therefore,
لذلك،
the royal heir the Empress is carrying
الوريث الملكي الإمبراطورة تحمل
shall ascend the throne.
سيعتلي العرش.
You petty man who fabricates history!
أيها الرجل التافه الذي يصنع التاريخ!
Guards!
حراس!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
For a waiting maid
لخادمة انتظار
to be dressed by others before death,
أن يرتديها الآخرون قبل الموت،
I suppose that's a proper end, right?
أعتقد أن هذه نهاية مناسبة، أليس كذلك؟
Dress her.
ألبسها.
Yes.
نعم.
The Prince Regent has arrived.
لقد وصل الأمير الوصي.
Greetings.
تحيات.
- Greetings, Your Highness.
- تحياتي، سموكم.
You've all endured a long journey.
لقد تحملتم جميعًا رحلة طويلة.
Efforts appreciated.
الجهود المبذولة محل تقدير.
Take your seats.
خذوا مقاعدكم.
His Majesty has arrived.
لقد وصل جلالته.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحياتي جلالتك.
Greetings, Your Grace.
تحياتي، صاحب السمو.
Rise.
يعلو.
Be seated.
اجلس.
Everyone!
الجميع!
Today marks a joyous occasion.
اليوم هو مناسبة سعيدة.
Our empire is blessed with divine signs and the impending royal birth.
إن إمبراطوريتنا مباركة بالعلامات الإلهية والميلاد الملكي الوشيك.
Let us raise our cups together
دعونا نرفع كؤوسنا معًا
to celebrate
للاحتفال
for His Majesty and Her Grace.
لجلالته ونعمته.
The envoys have traveled great distances to our nation.
لقد سافر المبعوثون مسافات طويلة إلى بلادنا.
Let us all enjoy this joyous occasion.
فلنستمتع جميعا بهذه المناسبة السعيدة.
Today, let formalities be set aside.
اليوم دعونا نضع الإجراءات الشكلية جانبا.
Enjoy the feast!
استمتع بالعيد!
Let the feast begin!
لتبدأ الوليمة!
His Highness said
وقال سموه
if you succeed in this mission,
إذا نجحت في هذه المهمة،
you'll be rewarded with titles and lands.
سيتم مكافأتك بالألقاب والأراضي.
Then we'll thank His Highness and you in advance.
ثم نشكر سموه ولك مقدما.
The rest shall act when the cup shatters.
والباقي سيتصرف عندما تتحطم الكأس.
Strike immediately
اضرب على الفور
and kill Shi Yu.
وقتل شي يو.
Complete this,
أكمل هذا،
and you will enjoy wealth for life.
وسوف تتمتع بالثروة مدى الحياة.
- Yes!
- نعم!
Assassins!
القتلة!
Guard His Majesty!
احرس جلالته!
Guard Her Grace!
حافظ على نعمتها!
Capture the assassins alive
القبض على القتلة أحياء
at all costs!
بكل ثمن!
Remain calm, everyone.
حافظوا على هدوئكم، الجميع.
On this auspicious occasion,
وفي هذه المناسبة الميمونة،
assassins dared attack His Majesty.
تجرأ القتلة على مهاجمة جلالته.
This outrage cannot stand!
هذا الغضب لا يمكن أن يستمر!
I will give an account to everyone here
سأقدم حسابًا للجميع هنا
and also
و أيضا
to His Majesty.
الى جلالته.
Report!
تقرير!
Assassins have been captured.
لقد تم القبض على القتلة.
♪Without fate, this dream would fade♪
♪بدون القدر، هذا الحلم سوف يتلاشى♪
♪Without you, my life would quietly end♪
♪بدونك، حياتي ستنتهي بهدوء♪
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
♪Let fate cut like a blade♪
♪دع القدر يقطع مثل الشفرة♪
♪I bid you one last farewell♪
♪أقول لك وداعا أخيرا♪
♪I know not love's emptiness nor hatred's pain♪
♪لا أعرف فراغ الحب ولا ألم الكراهية♪
♪When we meet again, the snow will melt away♪
♪عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى، سوف يذوب الثلج♪
♪One vow, so deep in love♪
♪عهد واحد، عميق في الحب♪
♪I'd give my life for it♪
♪سأعطي حياتي من أجله♪